

# MIRZA AHTSHAM

Website Developer & Graphic Designer .





### **EXPERIENCES**

TOP KII T

April 19 - Oct 19

NORTH GATE WAYS July, 2018

**KILTS MASTER** 

2016 - 2018

I REPAIR YORK
Eeb.2023

2013 - 2016

**ECOMMERCE PHOTO GALLERY** 

https://topkilt.com/

Major Job Was Digital Marketing Manager & Website Developer & Designer. I make this Project from Scratch. Add all the Product Posts, Image Gallery, Coupon and Videos.

TRAVEL & TOUR AGENCY IN PAKISTAN

https://northgateways.com/

Major Job Was Website Developer & Designer. I make this Project from Scratch as per client requirements.

**ECOMMERCE BRAND** 

https://kiltmaster.com/

Major Job Was Digital Marketing Expert.

Do on-page and Off-page SEO. Add Many New Arrival

Products.

**MOBILE REPAIR SHOP IN UK** 

https://irepairyork.com/

Major Job Was Website Designer and Developer. Build this amzing Website from scratch using Premium Theme and Custome with WP Backery Builder.

#### **EDUCATION**

GCT MULTAN

**DIPLOMA OF ASSOCIATE ENGINEERING** 

Major Sunject Was Lathe Machine, Saftey, CNC Machine, Drawing. Practical Work Was Wood Work, Welding,

Machine Operations.

GOVT H\S SHER SULTAN MATRICULATION

2009 - 2010 Major Subject Was Mathimatics, Chemistery, Biology,

 $Physics.\ Practical\ Work\ was\ Make\ Oxygen\ Gas,\ Draw\ Sketch$ 

of Body Organs ETC.

PVTC BASIC IT LITERACY COURSE

2017 Practical Work Was Understand the input and Output

Devices of Computer, Work on Word, Power Point and Excel, Basic Knowledge of Installing Operating System. (Windows)

#### REFERENCE

**ALI RAZA JANJUA** 

Director, Founder of **Kilt Master** Phone: +312 6605654 Email: arjanjua1@gmail.com **ZAKKI MUGHAL** 

Web developer at **Scottish Kilt Shop** Phone: +321 9444437

Email: zakki098@gmail.com

#### **ABOUT ME**

Greetings! My Name is Mirza Muhammad Ahtsham. A Professional WordPress, Graphic Designer, Illustrator and Photoshop expert With almost 6+ years of experience in this field. I Believe In Quality, Rather Than Quantity. I can create a fully responsive WordPress Website & know how to play with the PREMIUM THEMES. I can fix any type of Customization & Difficulties that you're facing in your WordPress.

#### **CONTACT**

Address:

ITEHAD Colony Lahore Punjab, Pakistan

Mobile:

+92 300 2092384

Whatsapp:

+92 346 4784039

Email:

mirza.ahtsham786@gmail.com

Website:

www.ahtsham.me

Skype:

mirza.ahtsham786

#### **SKILLS**

Wordpress
Blogger
Photoshop
Illustrator
SEO -SMO

#### **LANGUAGE**

English Urdu

# WEBSITE DESIGN & DEVELOPMENT EXPERIENCES

**MEDMAX TECHNOLOGIES** 

MEDICAL BILLING AGENCY

Jan, 2023 - Continue

Jan. 2023 - Continue

https://medmaxtechnologies.com/

I Restructure this Whole Website. Create and Design new Landing Page as per instruction. Improve the website Speed. Current website Speed Is 1.5 Sec on Desktop and less then 3 Sec on Mobile.

**SMAG TECHNOLOGIES** 

**DIGITAL MARKETING SERVICES PROVIDER** 

https://smagtechnologies.com/

I am working here as a Sr. Website Designer and Developer. I created a Logo for SMAG Technologies. It is a Digital Marketing Agency. I loved to work with SMAG Technologies Team. Very Cooporative and Good in Comunication. I create this from scratch. Design and Develope unique Sutructure and Optimize the Speed. Now its Speed is less then 2 Sec.

**SEED GOC** April, 2023 **GEMS STONE, NATURAL MINIRALS AND MARBLE** 

https://seedgoc.com/

I created this Website as per Client Requirments from the Scratch. Create Specific Landing Page Functionality and Create Popup Functionality with Dynamic Contact Form.

**UTS EXPORT** 

April, 2023

**IMPORT EXPORT BUSINESS** 

https://www.utsexport.com/

I created a this Website from the scracth. I collect all the Content and data from the Client and then finalize the design and Complete this Project with in a 7 Working Days.

**ABLE ESTIMATING** 

**CONSTRUCTION AGENCY** 

June, 2023

https://ablestimating.com/

I created a this Website from the scracth. I collect all the Content and data from the Client and then finalize the design and Complete this Project with in a 7 Working Days

**ECO NIMES** 2009 - 2010

**CLOTHING BRAND** 

https://econimes.com/

I created a this Website from the scracth. I collect all the Content and data from the Client and then finalize the design and Complete this Project with in a 15 Working Days.

**GRAPHIC DESIGN WALI** 

**GRAPHIC DESIGNER FREELANCER PORTFOLIO** 

https://graphicdesignwali.blogspot.com/

I created this website Using Google Blogger Platform. It was an amazing Experience to Customize Blogger Website As per Client Requirements. Many Custom Element Included as per Need.

**REFERENCE** 

Mar, 2020 - Continue

**ABRAR UMER** 

Director, Founder of **Eco Nimes** Phone: +92 300 0443389 Email: abrar.umer@econimes.com **MAHREEN SIDDIQUI** 

Co-Founder of **SMAG Technologies** 

Phone: +92 324 4323239

Email: mahreen-siddiqui@smagtechnologies.com

**SKILLS** 

HTML5 - CSS3

**Tailwind CSS** 

Wix

## **GRAPHIC DESIGN EXPERIENCES**

**DIGITAL PAKISTAN SUMMIT** 

SOCIAL MEDIA CONTENT CREATION

Oct'20 - Mar'21

https://www.facebook.com/digitalpakistansummit1/

I Joined **Digital Pakistan** Organisation as Graphic Designer. My Primary Job is Make website post, banners, Social Media Posts, Edit Product images, Social MediaMarketing. I love to design logos, and Graphics.

**SMAG TECHNOLOGIES** 

**DIGITAL MARKETING SERVICE PROVIDER LOGO DESIGN** 

Jan, 2023

https://smagtechnologies.com/

I created a Logo for **SMAG Technologies**. It is a Digital Marketing Agency. I loved to work with SMAG Technologies Team. Very Cooporative and Good in Comunication.

**METHY AAM WALA** 

Mav'21 - Jun'21

Jun.2023

2018 - 2020

**FACEBOOK ACCOUNT CREATION, OPTIMIZATION & CONTENT CREATOR** 

https://www.facebook.com/meethyaamwala/

I created a FB Business Page, Optimize it. Then Start Create Unique and Attractive Content Creation. Post for **Methy Aam Wala** Facebook Business Page. 2 Posts a Day...

**MEDMAX TECHNOLOGIES** 

CREATE PROMOTIONAL FLYER, BANNER, STANDEES FOR AN EVENT

https://medmaxtechnologies.com/

I created a Standees and Flyer for Medmax Technologies. I was a Good

Experience to work for Medmax technologies Team...

**HONEY WORD PK** 

WEBSITE GRAPHICS AND SOCIAL MEDIA CONTENT CREATION

https://www.facebook.com/honeyworldpk/

I created all the Graphics elements of Honey World PK Project. Design Logo, Create Social Media Accounts Optimize all Account and Then Start

Create Content for All Platforms.

**B2B SYSTEMS** 

2009 - 2010

2021 - 2022

LOGO DESIGN AND WEBSITE CUSTOM GRAPHICS CREATION

https://graphic design wali.blog spot.com/2023/02/flat-minimal ist-logo-design-58.html and the state of the

Created a Attractive logo for B2BSystems. Create Some Website

Elements and

**FUNPACK TRAVELS** 

CREATE LOGO, SOCIAL MEDIA ACCOUNTS, CONTENT & WEBSITE GRAPHICS

https://www.facebook.com/funpacktravels

I create Unique logo for this Project. Create all Social Media Accounts, Optimize all the Accounts and start Creating Content. Create Custom Graphics for a Website. Build Website for this Project As well.

**REFERENCE** 

**MUDASSIR MIRZA** 

Director, Founder of **B2BSystemsItd** Phone: +92 349 7147200

Email: hello.mudassirmirza@gmail.com

HAMZA SIDDIQUI

Founder of **A1kilts**Phone: +92 303 7449648
Email: a1kiltsss@gmail.com

**SKILLS** 

Canva Pro

Camtesia

**Youtube SEO**